

# ESTIPULAR AARON

Web Designer & Front-end frontend web developer

#### CONTACT

- 09297280335
- aaron.estipular31yahoo.com
- https://aaron3194.github.io/ae
  portfolio/

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## HTML APPLICATION DEVELOPER

E-team workforce - Accenture | Nov 2021 - August 2022

- -Migrate sitecore website to Adobe experience manager
- -Create html codes with html code components
- Recreate Accenture website to new platform Sitecore to Adobe Experience Manager.
- Creating widgets and components header and footer for geos
- Coordinating with team
- development and implementation for the product application

## **WEB DEVELOPER**

EnfraUSA Solutions, Inc. | Jan 2021- June 2021

- Creating website for therapy website
- Migrate legacy website to october CMS
- Developing and editing images
- Working on the usability, development and testing websites
- Website optimization

# PROCESS EXECUTIVE

Personiv Manila / Nov 2018 - Jan 2019

- Helping with day-to-day search engine marketing or sem plus
- Providing boost business in every county using google adwords and pay per click for search engine using.

## **WEB DESIGNER**

Personiv Manila / Sep 2017 - Nov 2018

- Create website using duda a CMS platform
- Provide web design for yellow pages
- -Migrating old website to a modern web design
- -Recreate logos and images optimization
- -Provide client web design and website for client satisfactory

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Lyceum of alabang / 2012 - 2017

## **SECONDARY**

Colegio Dela Nuestra Senora De Guadalupe / 2008 - 2012

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

To be employed in a highly rewarding career where I can utilize my Skills and knowledge for career and self-growth. I am a qualified and professional web designer with experience in frontend coding. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

#### EXPERTISE

Web Design Graphics Design front-end coding Google Search

### SOFTWARE KNOWLEDGE

Graphic Design Software
Software for Design
Content Management System
Team Communication Sofware
Graphics Software
Microsoft Application
CRM Application
Code Editor Application

## PERSONAL SKILLS

Creativity
Team building
Problem Solving